<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Chartam Input Output - chartamio</title>
        <link>https://chartamio.org</link>
        <description>This package provides a comprehensive chart library built on top of amCharts 5, a powerful and
            flexible React charting library that supports a wide range of chart types and data formats. With this
            library, you can easily create visually stunning and interactive charts for your web applications,
            dashboards, and reports. The library includes a variety of pre-built chart types, such as bar charts, line
            charts, scatter charts, and more, that can be customized to fit your specific needs. The package is designed
            to be easy to use and integrate into your existing web development workflow. It comes with comprehensive
            documentation and examples to help you get started quickly.</description>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <atom:link href="https://chartamio.org/sitemap.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
            <title>Getting Started - Overview</title>
            <link>https://chartamio.org/getting-started/overview</link>
            <description>This package provides a comprehensive chart library built on top of amCharts 5, a powerful and
                flexible JavaScript charting library that supports a wide range of chart types and data formats. With
                this library, you can easily create visually stunning and interactive charts for your web applications,
                dashboards, and reports. The library includes a variety of pre-built chart types, such as bar charts,
                line charts, scatter charts, and more, that can be customized to fit your specific needs. The package is
                designed to be easy to use and integrate into your existing web development workflow. It comes with
                comprehensive documentation and examples to help you get started quickly.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Getting Started - Installation</title>
            <link>https://chartamio.org/getting-started/installation</link>
            <description>Install chartam.io, the world's most popular React chart library .</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Getting Started - Usage</title>
            <link>https://chartamio.org/getting-started/usage</link>
            <description>Learn the basics of working with chartam.io components.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Our Contributers</title>
            <link>https://chartamio.org/getting-started/contributers</link>
            <description>We welcome contributions from the community! If you find a bug, have a feature request, or would like to contribute code, please open an issue or pull request on our GitHub repository.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Our Sponsors</title>
            <link>https://chartamio.org/getting-started/sponsors</link>
            <description>Join us as a sponsor of char6tam.io and discover the benefits of partnering with a leading data visualization library.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Column with Rotated Labels</title>
            <link>https://chartamio.org/charts/column-with-rotated-label</link>
            <description>Beautiful bar chart with column with rotated labels category wised data.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Simple Date Line Graph</title>
            <link>https://chartamio.org/charts/date-line-chart</link>
            <description>Line graph (also known as Line chart) displays series of data points connected by straight line segments.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Category Line Graph</title>
            <link>https://chartamio.org/charts/category-line-chart#single-line-chart</link>
            <description>Line graph (also known as Line chart) displays series of data points connected by straight line segments.</description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>